ytmonster.net 2019-12-12

# YTMonster® | Privacy Policy

In addition to the above, we may disclose your personal information to the following parties and under the following circumstances:

We are the Data Controller for Master Data that you enter creating and maintaining your profile, which includes, but is not limited to, your username, password, email address, and the registration of your IP address.

We are also the Data Controller for the information passed on to other services. Danish data protection legislation regulates our collection of your information together with GDPR.

**3.2 Information for which you are the Data Controller**

You are the Data Controller of the information that you choose to publish on the Site and the personal information disclosed when you link your Social Network Profile(s) to your profile on the Site.

* * *

4\. Links to other websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. Our inclusion of such links does not imply our endorsement any of those websites. We do not control the content of these Third Party websites and assume no responsibility for the Third Party or their policies or practices.

We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these Third Party websites as their personal data collection, handling and processing procedures may differ from ours.

* * *

5\. Data processors and transfer of personal data outside the EU

We use external companies to maintain the technical operation of our Site and our services. These companies are Data Processors for the personal data for which we are Data Controllers. By accepting this Policy, you agree that we may also allow the information you are the Data Controller of to be processed by these Data Processors.

We have entered into Data Processing Agreements with the Data Processors, and it follows from these agreements that they must act exclusively in accordance with our instructions. By accepting this Policy, you authorize us to give such instructions to Data Processors to process information in accordance with this Policy when using our Site.

The Data Processors have taken reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect the information from accidental or illegal destruction, loss or deterioration, and to protect the information against disclosure to unauthorized persons, abuse, or other treatment in violation of data protection laws. At your request - and possibly against remuneration at the Data Processors’ current hourly rates for such work - the Data Processors must provide sufficient information to you to demonstrate that the above mentioned technical and organizational security measures have been taken.

Some of these Data Processors are located outside the European Union, such as in the United States. You consent to use Data Processors in insecure third countries, provided there is a legal basis for the transfer of your personal data, ensuring adequate protection of them, for example if the Data Processor is part of the EU-US Privacy Shield scheme.

* * *

6\. Data storage

We keep the Master Data and other personal information you provide, including your campaigns, for as long as you have an Account or necessary to provide our services to you. We delete this information at your request, except for financial transaction information, which we are required to store for ten (10) years. All other information will be deleted.

Although you close your Account, we will in certain cases choose to keep some information (such as visits to our Site) in an anonymous or aggregated form.

* * *

7\. Safety precautions

We use reasonable organizational, technical, and administrative measures to protect your personal information in our organization, and we regularly review our system for vulnerabilities. But since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee or guarantee the security of the information you send to us. Emails sent through the Site may not be encrypted and we therefore advise you not to include any confidential information in your emails to us. We always work to improve our security procedures and we update this information as these practices evolve over time.

* * *

8\. Cookies

The Site uses cookies and similar technologies ("Cookies"). By using our Site, you accept that we use Cookies as described below.

**8.1 What types of Cookies do we use?**

Cookies are small pieces of information that the Site places on your computer's hard drive, on your tablet, or on your smartphone. Note that HTML5 has introduced Internet storage, that has properties similar to Cookies, and that we therefore consider this a cookie in the following.

Cookies contain information that the Site uses to make communication between you and your web browser more effective. Cookies identify your computer or device instead of you as an individual user.

We use session cookies, persistent cookies, HTML5 sessionStorage, and HTML5 localStorage session cookies. Persistent cookies are permanent and stored and remain on your computer until they are deleted. Persistent cookies expire or delete themselves automatically after a certain period of time, set per cookie, but renewed each time you visit the Site. HTML5 localStorage objects are permanent and remain on your computer until they are deleted.

**8.2 What do we use Cookies for?**

We use Cookies for:

**8.2.1 Generation of statistics**

Site Traffic Measurement such as the number of visits to the Site, which domains the visitors come from, the pages they visit on the Site, and the overall geographical areas the visitors are located.

**8.2.2 Monitor Site Performance and Your Use of Our Site**

Monitoring the Site, application performance, and how you use our Site applications.

**8.2.3 Approval and improvement of the functionality of our Site**

Optimizing your experience with the Site, which includes remembering your username and password when you return to the Site, as well as remembering information about your browser and preferences.

**8.2.4 Connect with Social Networks**

Allowing you to connect with Social Networks, such as YouTube.

**8.3 Third Party Cookies**

Third Party cookies are set by Third Party websites - not our Site. When you visit our Site, the following Third Party cookies can be set:

  * Facebook cookies

**8.4 Deleting Cookies**

You can delete the Cookies that are already on your device. You can usually delete Cookies from the Privacy or History area available from the Settings menu or Browser options. In most browsers, the same menu can be accessed via the keyboard shortcut Ctrl + Shift + Del or Command + Shift + Del if you are using a Mac.

Please note that if you do not accept Cookies from our Site, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site, and you may not be able to access some of its features.

* * *

9\. Access to and insight into the personal data we hold about you

If you have an account on YTMonster®, you can log into your Account and see what information we hold about you, including your campaigns, and why we keep that information.

If you do not have an Account, you can send an email to [privacy@ytmonster.net](mailto:privacy@ytmonster.net), and request information about your personal information. When we receive your request, we will tell you which personal information we hold about you, how we collect the information, the purpose for which we process your personal information, and who we share your personal information with.

* * *

10\. Download your personal information (data transferability)

If you have a user profile on YTMonster®, you can download the personal information you provided to us, including your campaigns.

* * *

11\. Correction and deletion of your personal information

If the Master Data or other personal information we hold about you in our capacity as Data Controller is inaccurate or misleading, you can correct most of the information through your Account. We recommend that you correct the information yourself. Otherwise, feel free to ask us to help correct your information.

You may at any time correct or delete any content and personal information on the Site for which you are the Data Controller (see 3.2). If your personal information changes, or if you no longer wish to appear on the Site, you may update or delete the information by logging into your Account.

Once your Account is deleted, all information associated with your Account will be deleted, including your Master Data, campaigns, and other communications on the Site. We delete this information at your request, except for financial transaction information, which we are required to store for ten (10) years. All other information will be deleted.

We reserve the right to block access to your Account and / or delete it if the Account or content associated with your Account or your campaign(s) on the Site, in our opinion is, discriminatory, racist, sexually oriented, unethical, threatening, offensive, harassing or otherwise violating applicable laws, third-party rights or our user policies, or is incompatible with the purpose of the Site.

* * *

12\. Other Rights

In addition to the rights set forth above, with respect to your personal data, you also have the following rights:

  * You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and to limit the processing of your personal data
  * In particular, you have an unconditional right to object to the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes
  * If our processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you are entitled at any time to withdraw your consent. Your withdrawal does not affect the legality of the processing of information that was performed before you withdrew your consent. You can withdraw your consent by sending an email to [privacy@ytmonster.net](mailto:privacy@ytmonster.net)

Under certain circumstances, these rights may be limited or contingent. For example, whether you are entitled to data transferability in a particular case depends on the specific circumstances of the processing activity.

* * *

13\. Children's information

Our Site is not intended for children. If you become aware that a child under 13 has given us their personal information, please contact us by email to [privacy@ytmonster.net](mailto:privacy@ytmonster.net).

* * *

14\. Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy. The date displayed at the end of this Policy indicates when it was last revised. If we make significant changes to it, we will notify you through our Site or otherwise, to allow you to review the changes before they come into effect. If you object to our changes, you may close your Account. Your continued use of our Site after we publish or post a notice of changes to the Policy means that you agree to the updated Policy.

* * *

15\. Contact information and where you can send questions or complaints

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Policy, how we treat your personal information, or would like us to correct your personal information, please contact us at: [privacy@ytmonster.net](mailto:privacy@ytmonster.net).
